Did you enjoy this week's video?
Plan for the next week?
Cooking video?
Hello.
Can I give you this before explaining
the project?
What is it?
I messed up.
We made a phone call.
We did it once at E-BINZU.
I miss it.
We were wondering if the message would
reach the roof from the 4th floor garden
terrace.
It was a live broadcast.
We were shooting a live broadcast.
That's the 4th to 10th floor.
For those who haven't seen the other
videos, it's about 800m high.
It's really high.
I'm scared.
I think you got permission.
I got permission.
They are coming.
How can I escape?
I'm here.
We ran from 4th to 10th floor.
Yes.
I was curious how far I can hear the
phone.
I will verify it.
You are like a YouTuber.
How far can I hear the phone?
One person is on the receiving side,
waiting at this starting point, and the
other person is with Ito.
Are you okay? Isn't it messed up?
It's messed up!
I'm going to untie it a little, but if
I can't talk after I've extended it all,
the video may be a boss, so I'll talk
and move on.
The limit of Ito's phone is that you
can't hear it.
We have to decide who will eat and who
will talk.
And we have to divide the team.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Let's divide the team.
Let's go!
Have a good trip!
I did a congratulation.
What?
It's funny.
It's my first time.
Hina?
Yes, it's my first time to do this.
Oh, I see.
Let's do it here.
Wait, wait, wait.
Which one is Hina?
I can hear you.
Great.
I'll go there again.
I'm going to the roof of the building.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm going to run away.
Good luck.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I can hear you!
Can you hear me?
OK.
Let's go to the waterfall.
It's interesting.
It's fun.
It's great.
It's sloping.
It's windy.
It's windy and I'm tired.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Can you hear me?
I can hear you.
It's about 50 meters away.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I think I can hear it.
Are you listening to it?
I can hear it.
Wait a minute.
Please subscribe to this channel.
It's heavy.
Why did you come from the bottom?
Can you hear me?
Hello.
Thank you.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I think this is about 100 meters.
You are pulled by the rope.
You are pulling strongly.
I'm pulling strongly.
I'm Miu Futtani.
I can hear the sound of the wind.
The sound of the wind?
It's noisy.
I can only hear the sound of the wind.
Can you hear me?
I can hear you.
I can speak in this way.
I can see you.
I can't hear you.
You are so good.
I raised my hand because I heard you.
I'm getting tears.
Are you going to kiss me?
You are great.
Really?
I heard you.
You are great.
Please subscribe to this channel.
We are running to the beach.
Wow, it's long.
I think it's better to go that way.
I think so, too.
Why?
I don't know.
Because of the wind?
Please subscribe to this channel.
Good luck!
I'm going to start!
I can hear a small voice.
Can you hear me?
I can hear you.
I can hear you!
I'm going to start!
I don't need a phone.
I can't speak in front of 800 meters.
I can't hear you.
Really?
Can you hear me?
I can hear you.
I can't hear you.
Are you talking?
I want you to talk!
My voice is gone.
The second try.
She is doing it.
I am not talking.
I got it!
I can hear it!
I heard it!
You heard it?
That's amazing!
I heard this voice.
I got it.
Hold me tight.
What?
I can hear it.
I heard it.
I heard it!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'm going to talk now, so if you can
hear me, please talk back.
OK, I got it.
Let's go.
Can you hear me?
Go ahead.
I haven't heard that for a long time.
I heard a little bit.
She said she heard a little bit.
Did you hear a little bit?
I heard a little bit.
Talk to me.
Are you eating a snack?
Just a little bit.
Thank you for watching.
How is it?
I can't hear anything.
If I can't hear, they can't hear.
I think it's over.
I can't hear anything.
Rine is listening.
Let's say goodbye.
We are done.
They are going to the next place.
The wind is gone.
I can hear you.
Please listen to my voice.
I want you to hear my voice.
I can't hear you.
Please.
I can hear you.
Rine.
I can't hear you.
I can hear you, but the wind is louder.
The wind is bad.
I can hear only the sound of the wind.
We have to go back.
Who do you like?
Please answer in 5 seconds.
3, 2, 1, go!
I can hear you but I don't know what
you are saying.
So my point is, looking down only at
the front of the boat is sexy
I can hear it!
Can you say it again?
Can you hear it?
I can hear it!
I can't eat it.
I think so.
Can you say it again?
Shiritori, Ringo, Gorilla, Zappa,
Parsley, Ringo, Gorilla, Zappa, Parsley,
I'm shiritori.
Can you hear it?
I'm bored.
I'm desperate.
I can't hear it.
Are you talking?
Are you shiritori?
I can't hear it.
Are you talking?
I'm hungry.
I ate a lot of sweets.
I'm full.
I'm going to eat a lot of sweets.
I'm pulling the rope too hard.
I'm going to fall.
well, we will see sea girls here
Make the most of what you have!
Oh, noises!
Do you hear that?
I hear it.
It was here.
Where are the tiles?
Let's count when you hear it.
Well, this is the rim.
I heard up to number 5.
Yay!
The bottom tile was about 5 meters.
Yasumori-san counted and came back.
How many tiles were there?
36 tiles.
Tachibana-san, what is 36 × 5?
6×30, 3×6, 3×2, 3×5.
It's about 150.
Thank you for watching!
Wait, wait.
Come back to swim.
362m.
380m.
Yes.
The result is...
180m.
Wow!
Great!
I thought there would be more.
If there was no wind,
I think we could go further.
If we improve it,
we can go further.
I want to go to the sea.
I want to go to the city where there is
no wind.
I agree.
If there is someone who can lend us
a place with long distance without
wind...
I think so.
I'll ask for it.
The result of today's verification
is...
We could hear the sound of the
telephone
even though the wind was strong.
We could hear the sound of the
telephone
and it was amazing.
Please try to verify it.
Please use it.
Yes.
We, Minami-gundan, will continue to
verify.
We will.
Thank you.
She is from the world of war.
Thank you for watching.
See you next week.
Bye bye.